<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://kirti91.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://kirti91.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-07T16:57:10+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://kirti91.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[IT NEWS.]]></title>
    <link href="http://kirti91.github.io/blog/2013/06/07/it-news/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-07T13:04:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://kirti91.github.io/blog/2013/06/07/it-news</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><html>
<body></p>

<h2>* Red Hat packages newer versions of Ruby,Python </h2>


<hr>


<h3>Software Collections 1.0 is designed for developers seeking access to cutting-edge progamming tools with support.</h3>


<p>Red Hat has put out a beta release of Software Collections 1.0, in a bid to let developers use newer versions of languages such as Ruby and Python with support.<br>
For certain applications, a more recent version of a language than what&#8217;s included in the base Enterprise Linux (RHEL) system is needed, according to Red Hat. Software Collections 1.0 is the first in a series of releases designed to allow developers to take advantage of new capabilities in their Web apps faster with the safety net of support from Red Hat, it said.</p>


<p>The beta includes access to the latest stable versions of Ruby 1.9.3 with Rails 3.2.8; Python 2.7 and 3.3; PHP 5.4; and Perl 5.16.3. Developers can also get their hands on a technology preview of node.js version 0.10. It is available now for use with RHEL 6 to customers with the right RHEL, Workstation or developer-related subscriptions. With the exception of Node.js, all components are supported. They are functionally complete and intended for production use.<br>
The included versions of Ruby and the related web application development framework Rails, have substantial performance improvements for faster load times. Python 3.3 offers significant improvements in language consistency and Perl version 5.16.3 has enhanced security, according to Red Hat.<br>
Additionally, Software Collections 1.0 also includes access to MariaDB version 5.5, MySQL version 5.5 and PostgreSQL version 9.2. Software Collections doesn&#8217;t replace the default system tools provided with Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6. Instead, a parallel set of tools are installed and can be optionally enabled by the user, Red Hat said.<br>
A major version of Software Collections will be released approximately every 18 months, and each version of a selected component remains backward compatible, according to Red Hat. The life cycle for version 1.0 will be three years.
</p>


<h2>* Hacker publishes alleged zero-day remote code execution exploit for older Plesk versions</h2>


<hr>


<h3><i>The exploit targets a vulnerability that only affects unsupported Plesk versions, the software&#8217;s creator said</i></h3>


<p>A hacker released what he claims is a zero-day exploit for older versions of the Parallels Plesk Panel, a popular Web hosting administration software package, that could allow attackers to inject arbitrary PHP code and execute rogue commands on Web servers.<br>
The hacker uses the alias &#8220;Kingcope&#8221; and has published exploits for unpatched vulnerabilities before.</p>


<p>The hacker claims the exploit was successfully tested against Plesk 9.5.4, Plesk 9.3, Plesk 9.2, Plesk 9.0, and Plesk 8.6 used in combination with the Apache Web server software on 32-bit and 64-bit Linux distributions including Red Hat, CentOS, and Fedora. However, Parallels, the Seattle-based company that develops Plesk Panel, claims that Plesk 9.5 and later versions are not affected by the exploit.
<br>&#8220;This vulnerability is a variation of the long known CVE-2012-1823 vulnerability related to the CGI mode of PHP only in older Plesk [versions],&#8221; a Parallels representative said Thursday via email. &#8220;All currently supported versions of Parallels Plesk Panel 9.5, 10.x and 11.x, as well Parallels Plesk Automation, are not vulnerable.&#8221;
<br>
According to a page on the company&#8217;s website, version 8 of the product has not been supported since September 2012 and Plesk version 9 will reach end of life Sunday.<br>
Even if the latest versions of the software are not affected, widespread exploitation of this vulnerability is still likely to happen because servers running the old and affected versions of Plesk are unlikely to be regularly maintained, said Craig Williams, a threat researcher at Cisco, </p>


<h2>* Android antivirus products a big flop, researchers say</h2>


<hr>


<h3><i>
Android smartphones and tablets are under attack, but the most popular tools developed to protect them are easily circumvented.</i> </h3>


<p>By Bob Brown | Network World</p>




<p>Android smartphones and tablets are under attack, but the most popular tools developed to protect them are easily circumvented, according to new research from Northwestern University and the University of North Carolina.<br>
The researchers created technology called DroidChamelon that can be used to perform common obfuscation techniques (simple switches in a virus&#8217;s binary code or file name, for example) to blow by security products. It tested DroidChamelon with products from AVG, Kaspersky, Eset, Symantec, and Webroot.</p>


<p>The results are quite surprising,&#8221; said Yan Chen, an associate professor of electrical engineering and computer science at Northwestern&#8217;s McCormick School of Engineering and Applied Science (Vaibhav Rastogi, a Ph.D. candidate at Northwestern, and Xuxian Jeng of North Carolina State University, coauthored the work with Chen). &#8220;Many of these products are blind to even trivial transformation attacks not involving code-level changes &#8211; operations a teenager could perform.&#8221;
<br>
The products&#8217; downfall was due to their use of overly simple content-based signatures, said researchers, who recommended more widespread use of static analysis to sniff out transformed viruses. The good news is that in 2012 tests, 45 percent of signatures could be evaded easily, whereas only 16 percent could be this time around.
<br>
Attackers are going after Android because it is so widely used. Kaspersky estimates more than 94 percent of all mobile malware targets Android. <br>
Even so, the researchers at Northwestern and North Catolina State emphasized that other mobile OSes are all aren&#8217;t necessarily any more protected from virus attacks. The researchers just didn&#8217;t test them.</p>


<hr>


<p><h>June 06, 2013</h></p>

<h2>Lenovo launches cloud storage service with access to social networks</h2>


<h3>The site will offer 5GB of free capacity and allow secure access</h3>


<p><h>By Lucas Mearian | Computerworld</h></p>

<p>Lenovo this week offered a peek under the covers on a new consumer cloud storage service called Lenovo Reach, which it said will allow users to securely access their cloud-based files and applications from any device via a single login ID.
<br>Beginning June 22, Lenovo said it will offer the Reach storage service to a limited number of users in order to garner feedback.<br>
Customers interested in a preview of Lenovo Reach can sign up now for the beta test.<br>
The Lenovo Reach personal cloud service will offer a single-sign on ID that allows users access to social networks, their online applications, as well as a search engine to help them find files, photos and other digital media across their online storage accounts.<br>
The new service can encrypt and remember all user IDs and passwords, offering users a method of accessing favorite websites with a single click.
<br>
&#8220;The intuitive interface is consistent across all user devices and is designed for touch as well as keyboard and mouse interaction,&#8221; Lenovo said.<br>
Lenovo Reach supports Microsoft Windows, Google Android, and iOS operating systems across Lenovo and non-Lenovo branded PCs, tablets, and smartphones.<br>
&#8220;Lenovo Reach makes it incredibly simple and convenient for people to interact with their growing libraries of digital content and apps from virtually anywhere, at any time, on any device through a consistent interface,&#8221; Mark Cohen, vice president of software and cloud solutions at Lenovo, said in a statement. &#8220;Lenovo Reach plays a fundamental role in our plan to expand cloud services to consumers around the world.&#8221;</p>


<p></body>
</html></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[hello]]></title>
    <link href="http://kirti91.github.io/blog/2013/06/03/hello/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-03T15:22:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://kirti91.github.io/blog/2013/06/03/hello</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><html>
<body>
<h> &hellip;How are ..You..!!! :&ndash;)&hellip;.</h>
<img src="http://www.dpcdsb.org/NR/rdonlyres/7E72E60C-8385-44EF-AB14-CF01F7BDF9EA/88305/welcom3.gif">
</body>
</html></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
